=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 13=
What is he doing here?
What is going on?
No idea.
This is mine.
My money.
Mine.
All mine.
Take a break.
Have some water, guys.
I bought you something to eat.
Yu Ming.
Today, either you die
or I do.
Sir.
He won't die here, will he?
No. No.
Look, his stomach is moving.
He is still breathing
and smiling.
Relax. Relax.
Don't scare yourselves.
Four of us here
draw too much attention.
You three go back first
and seal the tunnel.
Otherwise,
our place will be like
a public restroom.
Anyone could come in. Too dangerous.
Leave this to me. No worries.
Go.
Relax.
Hurry.
Nurse.
He passed out.
Is he your friend?
No. I don't know him.
I thought he was getting a perm.
He just passed out.
Please help him.
Dr. Zhang. Dr. Zhang!
We have a head injury here.
Sorry. I need to take this.
Ms. Zhang.
Hey, Mr. Yu.
I have been calling
your wife, but cannot reach her.
Where are you now?
Where are we?
After Baishi Service Area,
stay on the Zhoumin Expressway,
take the second exit to the camp.
It is easy to find.
Everyone is here.
Only you two.
Okay. Okay.
I got it.
Okay.
Ouyang.
Listen to me.
Hong Jinkui found the tunnel,
then crawled through it
into my house.
He found the money too.
Then he passed out.
So I brought him to the hospital.
And now,
Wenwen's teacher
needs Yitong and me there
for some event.
I need you to back right now
and keep an eye on the money.
I sent
three construction guys back
to fill the tunnel.
Get along with them.
You must protect
that money.
Some of it is Chen Zinuo's.
Whether she wants it or not,
I will give it to her.
Understand?
So...
Hurry up.
What is this
half-day camp tour?
It is a half-day tour at a camp.
Just the literal meaning?
Where is it?
Qiushan Resort.
The students take the bus,
and the parents drive there.
Wenwen never told us.
Why is this so sudden?
Maybe she feared
we'd embarrass her.
You are underestimating
your daughter.
She isn't afraid of being embarrassed.
She's afraid that once we go,
we will feel embarrassed.
She is protecting you.
You understand nothing.
Fine.
Then I will show her
how strong we are.
How is Jiang Juan?
I told her to go home and rest,
but my mom wouldn't let her.
She was afraid of getting beaten.
So now the two patients
are taking care of each other.
If you can call that care.
San.
What are you doing?
I was just thinking.
When will we ever have
this much money?
Mr. Yu let us
work here,
with the money right here.
That means he trusts us.
Don't get any ideas.
No way.
Come here.
I was just saying.
Guys.
There is noise upstairs.
Listen.
Who are you?
I'm Yu Ming's friend.
He sent me to help out.
Okay.
Then come down.
I'm fine up here.
A supervisor.
Get back to work.
Here, a big one.
You two share it.
Thanks, Dad.
Don't share it with others.
Wenwen.
The steak is ready.
Have some.
My dad grilled it. So good.
No.
Whatever.
Why are you here?
We wanted to have some fun too.
Why did you leave us out?
Your dad's steak is good.
But he means too well.
Just like the steak.
Overdone.
Too hard to swallow.
Too tough.
Well, medium-well
is not your taste, indeed.
You like it raw.
Raw? Yeah. We eat people.
I believe that.
You two
would absolutely do that.
Son.
This family
is kind of scary.
Come on. Let's go swimming.
The teacher said no swimming here.
Did she say we should get eaten?
Today,
I pass down to you
our family title,
the Water Swift.
Water Swift?
More like Water Pig.
What are you drawing?
Good.
The teeth are good.
This beef is imported, actually.
It tastes good.
Good?
It is tough as leather.
It is really not bad.
It has enough fat.
Try it.
No.
Wenwen, try it.
Eat it yourself.
Well, I misjudged him.
Son.
This is freestyle.
On your back is backstroke.
You try.
I'm scared.
I will show you a dive.
Dad.
Where is my watch?
Oh no.
Dad!
Cramp!
What is wrong, Dad?
Son, I have a cramp!
Help!
Help my dad!
Don't eat too much.
It would be a waste.
Can't let the cow die for nothing.
Help!
Want some seeds?
Save my dad!
Help!
What are you looking at?
What happened over there?
Help!
Save my dad!
Get more people.
Have them pull the rope.
Someone, help!
We need more hands!
Come on, hurry!
Someone fell in!
Hurry! Hurry!
Help! Help!
Don't move! Stay here!
Wenwen, stay still.
Yu Ming.
There is a rip current. Dangerous!
Come on!
I can do it.
Untie the rope.
Yes.
Here!
Don't tie it. No.
- Give it to me.
- Here.
Let it out. Feed the line!
Feed the line!
- Yes.
- Okay.
Dad!
Let it out!
More, more!
Slowly.
It is okay.
Your dad will be fine.
Slowly.
Dad!
Help!
Save...
Save my son first!
Grab the life ring first.
Save him!
Ring!
The ring!
He is almost up.
Careful!
Pull.
Pull, pull!
Pull harder! Come on!
Dad!
Yu Ming!
Hurry!
The boy is up!
We got the boy!
Come on, quick!
Slowly.
Slowly!
- It's okay.
- Careful.
Get him back.
Dad!
Pull!
Okay!
Pull! Hurry!
Hold steady. Pull hard.
Harder!
Pull it!
Yu Ming!
Dad!
Don't!
It is dangerous!
He is not out yet!
- Dad!
- Yu Ming!
Don't go!
Pull! Harder!
You can't go!
Pull up, then back!
- He is up!
- Give us a hand!
Drag him up!
Come on.
Put him here.
Dad!
My husband is still in the water!
He's still in the water!
My brother is dead.
I should stay mute forever.
It hurts so much.
So much.
Why was the one who died
not me?
- Calm down!
- Dad!
- Yu Ming!
- Dad! Dad!
I will raise Wenwen
as my own daughter
and bring her up.
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Yu Ming!
There! His head is up!
He is out!
- Yu Ming!
- Dad!
Help him!
Dad!
Save him!
Easy. Easy.
Pull slowly. Easy.
Easy.
Come on!
Come on, pull!
Did you think about
what we would do if you died?
Did that ever cross your mind?
I was trying to save them.
I panicked and jumped in.
I mainly wanted to save the boy.
That boy
is close to Wenwen
and treats her well.
But I could not save the boy
and leave his dad
in there, could I?
Do you know how your daughter
screamed on the beach?
I never want to hear
that sound again in my life.
I hope you remember that.
I will. I will.
It will not happen again.
Wenwen.
It's okay.
Our family lives long.
We will all live to 140.
There. There.
All right. All right.
No tears, okay?
Don't be scared.
Hello Kitty does not cry.
Why did you upset her?
Ma'am, go sit down.
Just wait a bit.
The ribs are almost ready.
I can handle this.
I'm fine.
Don't make me feel
useless.
I'm better now.
Strong as ever.
You just can't stop working.
You have been busy for years.
Take a break.
I'm not as capable as you.
Wait. I need to ask Jiajia.
Jiajia.
Anything you don't eat?
It's a little spicy.
I eat everything. I can handle spice.
Okay.
He stayed under forever.
Wenwen and I
were standing on the shore,
calling and calling.
We kept shouting.
He was holding his breath in the water.
We were holding ours on shore.
No one dared to breathe.
The way she screamed...
It was heartbreaking.
When she came back, she went inside
and wouldn't say a word to her dad.
I'm telling you,
Yu Ming makes me so mad.
He is going to be the death of me.
Why did he have to play hero?
What if he had not come back?
Always acting tough.
If he hadn't come back,
what would we do?
He has lost his mind!
Still mad at your dad?
I would be too.
But you need to know
that in that situation,
what he did was right.
But you were
really scared of losing him.
Right?
I know you are angry right now.
And you have a lot to say to him.
Go tell him.
Say it out.
Then you will not be so mad.
I'm taking a shower.
I'm warning you.
If you play hero again,
I really will stop talking to you.
I will make Mom, Grandma,
and my grandparents ignore you too.
Even kids know self-protection.
You're an adult.
Can you act like one?
Stop making everyone worry about you.
If something really happened to you,
I would support Mom remarrying.
Do you hear me?
Hurry up. Dad. I need you.
Got it.
I wasn't joking earlier.
I know.
I will be careful next time.
Not careful. Never again.
Okay.
Whatever you say.
What's wrong?
I'm not feeling inspired.
I can draw monsters, not people.
Then I will call
your mom over.
The teacher said to draw our father.
You can draw me
as a monster.
How about
you draw my brother?
Your biological father.
But I have no sense of him.
You have seen his photos.
I mean a feeling. A sense of him.
He had
very bright eyes.
No matter
where I was,
he could spot me right away.
He had such an easy smile.
With bright white teeth.
Congratulations, bro.
You have a little niece now.
I have a little niece!
When you have a concert,
we will sit in the front row.
We'll hold up your banner and shout,
"Yu Ming, I love you!"
Keep it down. Feng.
"You sing so well!"
Like that?
Not sharp teeth.
Round.
When I was little,
I was not very confident.
He would always encourage me.
When I was bad at sports,
he would tell me
I was good at singing.
When I was bad at math,
he would still tell me
I was good at singing.
When I was short,
he still said I sang well.
Because he kept encouraging me,
I became more and more confident.
In the end,
I became a singer.
People liked hearing me sing.
And I was happy.
Then later,
I got full of myself.
I bought
all those weird clothes,
ripped jeans,
and ragged outfits.
Your grandparents hated it.
The neighbors disliked me, too.
But he encouraged me again.
He said,
"While you are young,
be yourself.
When you are old,
you will not have the energy."
This is for you.
Thank you.
Sometimes I wonder,
he was young too back then.
How was he so amazing,
so smart?
He always knew
what I was thinking
and what I wanted.
But
I never once thought about
what he wanted.
Maybe
all he wanted was for us
to be happy.
He was very, very kind.
He always wanted to help others.
So,
if he had been there
today,
he would have done the same.
So he rubbed off on you.
Of course.
I'm his little brother.
And he was my big brother.
My hero, always.
She is asleep?
Yes.
Good.
Jiajia, we have something to say.
The 60 million is untouched?
Not a cent.
You really want my advice?
Yes.
Tell the police.
Jiajia is right.
Living on edge every day
is too much pressure.
If we drag this out,
it will only get worse.
Once the police come to us,
it's too late.
Then the whole thing changes.
Hiding that money
feels like carrying a boulder.
It's exhausting.
I want this weight gone.
Even if not for ourselves,
we have to think of our family.
Let's turn ourselves in.
I agree.
We will find Guo Li tomorrow
and tell her everything.
Couldn't we just text him?
Why write a letter?
It's different.
When Dad reads
this letter,
he can feel
the warmth of our regret.
What are you going to write?
I haven't figured it all out.
Right now,
all I can think of is,
"Dad,
by the time you read this,
we will already be in custody."
Okay.
"If we don't come out,
please take care of Wenwen."
That is all I have so far.
Add one more line.
"If the old woman starts trouble,
you must step in.
Remember that."
Maybe not "old woman" here.
Calling her "Mom"
would sound warmer.
Fine.
I'll go buy another one.
I need this file
by two this afternoon.
Okay.
Okay, thanks.
Did you check the surveil...?
Guo Li.
Wait.
She's busy. Hold on.
Tell me,
can you blame us for this?
It's obviously the bank's fault.
An ATM suddenly
spits out over 200 grand.
Anyone would lose their head.
Of course you take it.
After my wife took it,
the money was barely in our hands
before they called it theft.
They say she could get 4 or 5 years.
If she really goes in,
what are we supposed to do?
That is nothing.
Her brother-in-law
rented a small storefront
as a parcel station.
People always forget their packages.
There was one package
that sat there for months.
He was afraid it would mold,
so he kindly took it home
to keep it safe for the owner.
Who knew it was a luxury watch?
Worth over a million.
Now, the owner called the police,
saying he took the watch.
The police are investigating.
Unbelievable!
What are you two here for?
Well, I...
I have...
Hello?
What?
Five million?
That's an extremely large amount.
Ask a lawyer about the sentence.
Based on past cases,
at least ten years.
We give anti-fraud talks every day
and explain the legal consequences.
Why do these people
never listen?
Okay. I will ask for you.
That is terrifying.
60 million
could get us shot several times.
♪I shouldn't have shown off
before heaven.♪
♪I shouldn't have wrecked
the peach feast.♪
♪Now I suffer beneath the mountain,♪
♪only now knowing Buddha's power♪
♪reaches beyond the heavens.♪
What's wrong?
What?
Nothing. I have a cramp.
You scared me.
When I was little,
I stole money from my mom
to buy a toy.
I got it.
The whole way,
I ran toward the market.
But as I ran,
I got more anxious,
more scared.
I realized the fear
was far greater
than the joy of buying the toy.
So,
I turned around and ran home.
I put the money back.
To this day,
my mom still doesn't know it.
How about this?
We haven't touched the money,
right?
We put back
what was in the wall
and rebury
what was underground.
That way,
we can pretend
none of this ever happened.
It just started boiling.
Look at you,
having hot pot alone
in the basement.
How could I be alone?
This is my assistant, Money.
Yo, man.
Money. Money.
I'm here.
Say hello.
Hello.
How can I help you?
He has lost it.
I was bored.
Unbelievable!
No integrity.
I saw that whole room full of cash.
You don't pay me back,
but you sent someone to set me up?
Scum.
Scumbag!
Watch your mouth!
Have some manners!
Who are you talking to?
Who has no manners?
You.
This is a hospital, not your home.
Keep it down!
This is the way I talk.
None of your business.
It is my business.
You little punk.
Say it again?
- Come here!
- My fault!
- Come on!
- My bad!
I wouldn't dare.
Say it again!
I said I wouldn't dare.
Come here!
So rude.
Everyone can push me around.
Just because I stay quiet,
you think I'm a pushover?
Once I get rich this time,
I will make you all pay.
I will buy a villa.
A huge one.
I will buy a jet and a yacht.
When I fly first class,
I will buy two seats
and sleep all the way I want.
When I'm rich,
you're all dead.
Yu Ming.
I'll kill you!
Yu Ming,
screw you!
Yu Ming!
Open the door!
I'm here to make you pay!
Yu Ming!
Yu Ming! Open the door!
Come out and talk to me.
I'm here today
to die with you.
We shall perish together.
Come on. Come out!
If he wants to curse,
why throw in fancy words?
Makes him feel educated.
This money,
we have to
find out where it came from.
Otherwise,
we may die without knowing why.
So what we know now is
that the money involves
Hu Deshuai,
the construction workers,
and Zinuo and her mother.
Yu Ming, open the door!
I'm here for you!
Hu Deshuai is already dead.
Those three construction workers
don't seem fake.
The papers they had,
all those signatures,
the creases,
the aged look,
they looked old.
They didn't look fake.
Open the door, Yu Ming!
I'm here for you!
What are you looking at?
You are disturbing everyone.
Do you know that?
Then call the police.
Better yet,
go get the TV reporters
over here.
Thank you very much!
So unreasonable.
Yu Ming!
Yu Ming, open up for me.
Open the door!
Yu Ming, open up!
Yu Ming!
So now,
people who may know the truth
are Chen Zinuo and her mom,
right?
I think
we shouldn't ask her mom.
She looks too vicious.
Like a hungry she-wolf
on a rainy night.
Chen Zinuo is much better.
Her eyes
are like a curious
baby seal.
Let's ask her.
Me?
Who else?
Aren't you her future boyfriend?
No.
But if she confesses to me,
I may consider it.
How can you prove you own the place?
I have my ID.
Let me see it.
My ID is inside.
Without an ID,
how can I open the door?
Open the door first.
I will get my ID
and show it to you.
Then you will know
I'm the owner.
You have no proof.
I can't open it.
I have to call property management
and check.
Check what?
Why call anyone?
What are you, the police?
This is my house.
I filed a police report on it.
Are you trying to get me fired?
What...
Hey!
You! The property girl!
Come here.
What was your name again?
Zhao... Zhao Xiaolin, right?
Jiang Xiaoling.
Whatever. Come here.
Tell him.
Tell him
whether I own Unit 505.
He used to.
Used to?
What do you mean, used to?
Didn't I just pay you
the property management fees
for this place?
Back fees.
I still paid them,
didn't I?
Open it.
Come on. Open it.
Please don't, Mr. Hong.
Your house has been sold.
You are no longer the owner.
So what you mean is,
I'm not
the owner anymore, right?
Fine. Easy.
Then refund
my property management fees.
Right?
Come on. Refund me.
Pay me back.
No refund?
Then open the door.
Come on.
Sir.
You are not the owner anymore.
I can't help you.
Fine. I don't need you.
I will handle it myself.
Hey, stop!
Mr. Hong, you cannot do that.
Or I have to call the police.
Go ahead.
Call them or not,
I'm opening my own door.
What is wrong with that?
There are cameras everywhere.
If you pick the lock,
we have to call the police.
Fine.
Here.
Can't I rest here for a bit?
I'm dizzy.
I'll sit here for a while.
Mr. Hong.
You may rest here.
But
there are cameras all around.
Well,
we will
get going.
It's Zinuo's birthday today.
I have to go.
Wait.
That fat guy in black
is still sitting outside.
What do I do then?
Yu Ming, open the door!
You scum!
I know you are home, Yu Ming!
I'll take you out from the second floor.
Unbelievable! Yu Ming!
Yu Ming!
Open the door.
Open the door first.
Open it!
We can talk this out.
Okay, Yu Ming?
Yu Ming!
I see you, Yu Ming!
Open the door!
Why not just give him
the 1.02 million?
That's not
what he wants.
He wants the 60 million.
Yu Ming!
He's greedy and hungry.
Yu Ming, I see you!
You are behind the stairs!
Open the door, Yu Ming!
Yu Ming!
Screw you!
Let him shout.
Get your call.
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
Tiezhu.
Hello?
Mr. Yu.
That hole underground,
we have sealed it up.
About our money...
Listen.
I have a whole sack of problems now.
How about this?
We'll talk later.
I'll call you then.
Okay?
Hello? Sir?
Speak up.
Hello? Hello?
What did he say?
Not sure.
He said to call when we arrive,
then talk in person.
In person?
Eat then.
You can have it.
Okay, enough.
Why are you sneaking around?
I need you to test something.
It's Zinuo's birthday today.
I want to surprise her.
What is it?
Well?
Not great.
It feels like a nightclub.
It hurts my eyes.
Guess
how she will react.
Wow, so tacky.
Is it really that bad?
Bad.
Very bad.
A man
should be generous.
Learn from your dad.
Take her to luxury stores
and shop around.
Then a fancy restaurant
for dinner.
Then find a nice bar
and get a little tipsy.
And flowers.
Fill the whole room with them.
Stop making things up,
okay?
Help me out.
What gift should I give her?
No cheesy routines.
Once,
I liked a boy.
He made me a bowl of noodles
with a heart-shaped egg in it.
I still don't know
what magic was in that bowl.
After I ate it,
my whole stomach felt warm.
I was moved to tears.
Cried my makeup off.
You drank too much yesterday, right?
Do you know romance at all?
Bye.
Just a bowl of noodles.
Can it really work?
1,761 days.
Eating, sleeping,
working, and studying.
Those four things,
I did them all half-alive.
Every day, I stared at the bars
and thought about every step
I would take after getting out.
Nuo hates me
because she doesn't know
how cruel this world is.
But I do.
I was hard on her
so she would understand
the rules of this world.
Only when you are strong
can you avoid being controlled.
But she couldn't do it.
For five years,
I figured it out.
I was wrong.
She is my daughter.
She deserves comfort.
She deserves happiness.
She is too soft.
I was afraid people would bully her.
So Chen Liyang and I
worked ourselves to the bone.
We wanted to give her something
to lean on.
No matter how much she hates me,
I have to give her a better life.
She is my daughter.
No one gets to bully her.
I know
Chen Liyang
planted a mine back then.
It's all the evidence
he failed to destroy.
That mine,
once it falls into the wrong hands,
will explode.
And if it does,
this family falls apart.
Zinuo
will get nothing.
So you don't mind
that Zinuo reported you?
In the old days,
when people searched caves for treasure,
the child held the rope above
while the parents went down.
At the critical moment,
the kid would drop the rope and run.
Later, it became
the parents holding the rope
while the child went down.
That is how it should be.
No matter how much she hates me,
I have to do everything I can
to make her life better.
As long as she doesn't kill me,
she is still my daughter.
Mr. Chen
did leave something behind.
It is inside Unit 505.
But I don't know
where exactly.
(2018)
At a time like this,
you are still fixing that clock?
The cuckoo stopped calling.
I'm fixing it.
If it is broken, throw it out.
It sounds like a funeral wail.
No.
Nuo likes it.
When you are done, go to the study
and sort out all your ledgers.
The family of three...
All wolves.
I was the only fool.
(Next Episode)
(Actor, Guo Jingfei)
Hi, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
Cuckoo, cuckoo.
That clock.
The Black Forest Clock.
Could your dad
have hidden any clues
in it?
What's wrong?
That clock has been thrown away.
It kept going off randomly.
So we threw it out.
Where did you throw it?
A man and a woman came in the morning,
They were also looking for something
sent from your Ziyu Garden.
was a huge embezzler,
I didn't believe it.
Just how useless am I
that he'd find a way out
for me like this?
It really is Li Jin.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪